Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 5825
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1972-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold M.
5825
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3126416
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 18, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4191 AV: ILR School Audio-Visual Department Video Cassette Collection 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5512: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5620: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5659: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5775: NAA Records 5786: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5861: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5913: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5950: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases 5950 P: Arnold Zack Arbitration Cases Photographs 5979: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6004 OHT: NAA History Committee Oral History Interview Transcripts 6049: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases 6066: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6104: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6141: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 6205: NAA Committee Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Zack, Arnold.
3126416
- A - Bos Edison, 1986-87. (Box 1)
  - AAA Conference Honolulu, Hawaii Feb. 23 & 24, 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AAA- Labor Management Education Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AAA Discipline Issues Workshop New Orleans May 1, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AAA Summer Workshop Stratton, Vermont, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - AAA Hyannis Labor/Management Pro July 14-17, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A&P/UFCW Local #371 12/18/87 Burlington, VT, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Acushnet School Committee Acushnet Teachers Association, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Adams County School District and Teachers Association, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Advertising Corporation/ IUE Local 276 Holyoke, MA, 1959-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Advanced Arbitration Institute Honolulu, HA, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME/PA Independent Council Union Harrisburg, PA, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Davidson/ IAM Local 1790 Boston, MA, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Atlantic Super Value UCFW Local 592 Boston, MA, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic Richfield/ AIU Philly, 1982-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Atlantic Richfield/ AIU Philly, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Baker & Co./IOUE Local 4 Boston, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bailey Corporation/ UAW Hampton, NH, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bath Iron Works/ IUMSA, Local 6 Bath, Maine, 1978-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Berenson's Jai Alai Hartford, CT, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Berenson's Jai Alai/ Local 217 Hartford, CT, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Berenson's Hartford Jai Alai Local 217 Hotel Employees, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Berkshire Medical Center v. Carlos Merle Pittsfield, MA, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Boise Cascade/ United Paperworks Local 286 Philly, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Boston Edison/ UWUA, Local 369 Braintree, MA, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Boson School Committee: Boston Teachers Union Case No. 1139-0477-87, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Boston Edison/ UWUA Local 369 Braintree, MA, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Boston Edison/ Utility Workers of America Local 369 Dorchester, MA, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Boston & Maine Corporation/ IAM D & H, MeC, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Boston School Committee/ Boston Teachers Union, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Boston School Committee/ Boston Teachers Union, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Boston School Committee/ Boston Teachers Union, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Boston School Committee/ Boston Teachers Union, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Boston Edison UWUA # 369 Braintree, MA, 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Bost Ed. - Fed, 1986-87. (Box 2)
  - Boston School Committee/ BTU Local 66, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Boston School Committee/ BTU Local 66, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bradlee's/ UFCW Local #1445, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Town of Bristol/ UAW # 14852 A Seekonk, MA, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - British Air/ IAM, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Buffalo Eve, News: Buffalo Newspaper Guild, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Burlington Woods Convalescent/ RWDSU Local 1034, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cambridge Mediation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Carol Cable Company/ USWA #1130109085 S. Attleboro, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Catalytic/ IBEW Local 400 Philadelphia, 1973-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cherry Creek School District Education Association S.E. Denver, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - CEA Staff Org/ CEA Interest Arbitration, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chicopee Education Association Chicopee School Committee, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Children's Hospital/ 1199-C, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Colorado Education Association Fact Finding Training, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Coca-Cola/ Truck Drivers Auburn, MA, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Colorado Springs District 11 Fact Finding, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts v. National Association of Government Employees, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut State Board of Education and SVFT, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - CT/SVFT, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Continental Airlines/UFA Honolulu, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Continental Baking Co./ Boston BCTWU, Local 248, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Copley Plaza Hotel/ HRIEU & BU Local 26, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Danbury Hospital/ CSFT, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Dartmouth Educators Association School Committee, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Delaware Public Employees, Council 81, AFSCME, Local 49 v. New Castle County, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Denver Public Schools: Denver Teachers Association, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees v. Local 1199, RWDSU, AFL-CIO, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - District 1199/ Beth Israel Medical Center, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - DuPont/ Chemical Workers Association, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Endicott College/ Faculty Association, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Epping School Board/ Epping Education Association, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Fafnir Bearing Division, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Fed - Hormel, 1986-87. (Box 3)
  - Federal Paper Board Company vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Federal Paper Board Company vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Federal Paper Board Company vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union, 1956-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Filenes vs. UFCW Local 1445, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Franklin County Technical School Communication/ Vocational Teachers Association, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Frontier vs. ALPA Denver, CO, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Frontier vs. ALEA Denver, CO, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - General Dynamics vs. IUMSWA, 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - S.J. Flowers, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Golden Nugget Casino/ Carpenter's Local 623, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - B.F. Goodrich vs. Warehouse Employees Local 169, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Greyhound vs. ATU Columbus, Ohio, 1978-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Greyhound vs. ATU L.A., California, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Greyhound vs. ACGLU Phoenix, AZ, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Greyhound vs. ATU Park Plaza Hotel Boston, MA, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Greyhound vs. ATU 1225 San Francisco, CA, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Greyhound vs. ATU 1210 Philadelphia, PA, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Grinnell vs. IMAW Local 376 Lancaster, PA, 1973-1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Harley Davidson vs. IAMAW Local 175, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Harvard University vs. HRIEB Local 26, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Program on Negotiation at Harvard Law School, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Greyhound vs. ATU Local 1571 Cleveland, OH, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Greyhound Otis Walker Suspension Atlanta, GA, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Helmsley-Greenfield vs. Service Employees International Union Local 36, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Hendries Frozen Foods Truck Drivers Local 170, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hercules Cement vs. Local 22 UCL&G, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Hershey Chocolate Company vs. Chocolate Workers Local Union 464, 1971-1986 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - George A. Hormel & Company vs. UFCW Local P-9, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- HNS Mgmt - NH Yankee, 1986-87. (Box 4)
  - HNS Manage Company vs. AML Transit Union Local 425, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - IRRA Houston Continuing Education Center, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ITT Grinnell vs. IM&AW Local 376, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ITT Royal Electric vs. Electrical Workers Local 1196, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Kraft vs. Teamsters Local 380, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kraft vs. Teamsters Local 380, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lamoille Valley RR & UTC, 1973-1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Legal Aid Society vs. Association of Legal Aid Attorneys NYC, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Long Island University vs. LUI Faculty Federation, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - City of Lowell Police Department vs. IBPO Local 382, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Liquid Carbonic Corporation vs. Teamsters Local 249, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Litton vs. IAM & AW, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Manchester Knitted Fashions vs. ACTWU, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Market Forge Company vs. USWA, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Massachusetts Board of Regents 1139-1842-81, 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Mass Transit ADM vs. ATU Local 1300, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Mexico, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mobil Oil vs. Industrial Oil Workers, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Mobil Research & Development/ Mobilab Union, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Mobil Oil Corporation/ Industrial Oil Workers, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Mobil Oil/ OCAWIU Local # 8-766, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Nashua Association of School Principals/ Nashua School Board, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - National Practice Institute Hyatt Regency, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - New Castle County/ Delaware Public Employees AFSCME, 1978-1987 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - New Colonial Theatre Boston Musicians Association, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - N.H. Yankee (Seabrook) Painters & Allied, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - New York Public Employee Relations, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - New York City Ballet/ Local 802, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - N.H. Yankee Corporation/ International Union of Operating Engineers, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- NH - P, 1986-87. (Box 5)
  - N.H. Mediation, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - New Hampshire, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - NYSA and ILA, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - NWA/ BRAC Darryl Todd Case: System Board of Adjustment, 1979-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - NWA/ BRAC Cheryl Dudek Case: System Board of Adjustment, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - NWA/ BRAC Marilyn Bridge Case: System Board of Adjustment, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Package Machinery Company Local 220 IUE, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Pan American/ Union of Flight Attendants, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - City of Peabody/ IAFF Local 925, 1980-1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - PA Truck Lines/ Teamsters Local Union 25, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Old Rochester High School Mediation, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - PAN AM/ Independent Union of Flight Attendants, 1982-1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - City of Philadelphia/ AFSCME District Council 47, 1983-1988 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Petro & Jennings/ Plumbers Local 90, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Pillowtex/ UAW Local 376, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - School District of Philadelphia/ IBFO Local 1201, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Port Authority of NY & NJ/ Port Authority Benevolent Association, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Portsmouth Naval Shipyard/ Federal Employees Metal Trades, 1970-1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Procter & Gamble/ Industrial Oil & Chemical Workers, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Providence/ Public Service Employee, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Providence College, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pueblo School District 60, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Public Law Board 4068 Case 1 Maine Central RR/UTU, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Public Law Board 4068 Case 2 Maine Central RR/UTU, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Public Law Board 4068 Case 3 Maine Central RR/UTU, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Public Law Board 4068 Case 4 Maine Central RR/UTU, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Public Service Electrical & Gas Company 1330 1338 83, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Public Service Electrical & Gas System Council U2 IBEW, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Pueblo School District 60, 1983-1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- R-Z, 1986-87. (Box 6)
  - Rafferty-Brown Steel and USWA (Worcester), 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Rest Haven Nursing Home and N.E. Health Care Employees District 1119 Case No. 1130-2247-85, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Reverse School Committee and Revere Education Association, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - R Philharmonic and Providence Federation of Musicians, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rochester School Board and Rochester Federation of Teachers, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Rochester Telephone Company and CWA, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rochester Telephone and CWA, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Royal Electric Division IBEW Local # 1196, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Rust Engineering and Portland Ironworkers Local 496, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Sheraton and HRIE & BU, 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sinai Hospital of Baltimore and District 1199E, NUHHCE Case No. 1981-054, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Somerset School Committee and Somerset Teachers Association, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Standard Thompson Corporation IUE Local 274, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Standard Thompson Corporation IUE Local 274, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Star Porcelain and UERMWA, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Stone & Webster and Association of Engineers, Architects & Draftsmen Local 105, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Stone & Webster and Association of Engineers, Architects & Draftsmen Local 105, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Stone & Webster and Association of Engineers, Architects & Draftsmen Local 105, 1975-1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Stroehmann Brothers Company and Local 8 BCTWU, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Sun Olin Chemical Company and Oil, Chemical & Atomic Workers International Local 8-930, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Telegraph Publishing Company and International Typographical Union, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Tetley and FLM Joint Board, 1980-1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Trump Castle Casino Hotel & Restaurant Workers Local 54, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Trump Castle Casino Hotel & Restaurant Workers Local 54, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - TWA-IAM System Board of Adjustment-R, Gilchrist, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - TWA-IAM, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Trans World Airlines and IAM Littlejohn Discharge, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - TWA/ IAM System Board of Adjustment, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - TWA/ IAM System Board of Adjustment, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - TWA/ IAM System Board of Adjustment, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Union Carbide and Bound Brook O.C.A.W. Local 8-891, 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - US Air and AFA, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - United Telephone of NJ and IBEW, Local 827, 1981-1987 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Wilkinsburg-Penn Joint Water Authority and UWA Local 191, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- USPS, 1986-87. (Box 7)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - USPS/APWU, 1978-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - USPS/APWU, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - USPS/NALC, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - USPS/NALC, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - USPS/NALC, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - USPS/NALC, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - USPS/NALC, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - USPS/NALC, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - USPS/NALC, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - USPS/NALC, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - USPS/NALC, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - USPS/Rural, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - USPS/Rural, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - USPS/Rural, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Mirotta v. U.S. Postal Services Payment of Witness Fee, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - UPS/Mail Handlers, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- USPS, 1986-87. (Box 8)
  - USPS/ LIUNA, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - USPS/ LIUNA, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - USPS/ NALC, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1981-1986 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - USPS/Mail Handlers, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - USPS/APWU, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - USPS/APWU, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - USPS/APWU, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - USPS/APWU, 1974-1986 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - USPS/APWU, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - USPS/APWU, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - USPS/APWU, 1981-1986 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - USPS/APWU, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - USPS/APWU, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - USPS/APWU, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - USPS/APWU, 1983-1986 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - USPS/APWU, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- USPS, 1986-87. (Box 9)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1984-1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1979-1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - USPS/ Mail Handlers, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - USPS/NALC, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - USPS/APWU, 1978-1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - USPS/APWU, 1978-1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - USPS/APWU, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - USPS/APWU, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Yale University Local 34, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Yale University Local 34, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Yale University Local 35, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Yale University Local 35, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Yale University Local 35, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 30)